<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed"  >
      <channel>
          <title>Happy Maybe</title>
          
          <description><![CDATA[Happy Maybe is a conversational podcast where Vasily and Nikita share their unique insights on the winding journey of life. From cultural adaptation to navigating life&amp;apos;s obstacles, they explore existential issues and the complex nature of happiness.]]></description>
          <itunes:image href="https://happymaybe.com/images/happy-maybe-artwork-4-39393.jpg"/>
          <language>en</language>
          <copyright>Happy Maybe</copyright>
          <link>https://www.happymaybe.com/</link>
          <image>
              <url>https://happymaybe.com/images/happy-maybe-artwork-4-39393.jpg</url>
              <title>Happy Maybe</title>
              <link>https://www.happymaybe.com/</link>
          </image>
          <itunes:summary><![CDATA[Happy Maybe is a conversational podcast where Vasily and Nikita share their unique insights on the winding journey of life. From cultural adaptation to navigating life&amp;apos;s obstacles, they explore existential issues and the complex nature of happiness.]]></itunes:summary>
          <itunes:subtitle>Two friends discuss existential issues of life, free will, and overcoming obstacles, sometimes getting lost in questions and solutions.</itunes:subtitle>
          
          <itunes:owner>
              <itunes:name>Vasily Myazin and Nikita Chepanov</itunes:name>
              <itunes:email>contact@happymaybe.com</itunes:email>
          </itunes:owner>
          <itunes:author>Vasily Myazin and Nikita Chepanov</itunes:author>
          
          <itunes:category text="Religion and Spirituality">
              <itunes:category text="Spirituality" />
          </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Society and Culture">
              <itunes:category text="Personal Journals" />
            <itunes:category text="Philosophy" />
          </itunes:category>
          <itunes:keywords>meaning, existentialism</itunes:keywords>
          <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
          
  
          <item>
              <title>Breaking Bonds</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Ending relationships can be painful but sometimes vital. Vasily and Nikita discuss times when they cut ties and how to know when enough is enough.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode, Vasily and Nikita tackle the delicate topic of ending relationships. The conversation is sparked by a personal story of a road trip that resulted in a permanent falling out with another couple. This real-life example sets the stage for a broader discussion on the challenging decisions of cutting ties, especially when influenced by clashing political views and divergent worldviews in today's divisive climate.</p><p>Throughout the episode, the hosts engage in an introspective debate on the balance between self-preservation and the moral responsibility of staying connected. They ponder the fine line between creating a protective echo chamber and the necessity of distancing oneself for mental well-being. True to the podcast's nature, their exchange is raw and honest, mirroring the struggle between the human desire for connection and the essential act of setting boundaries. This episode of "Happy Maybe" resonates with the harsh reality that sometimes, ending relationships, however painful, is crucial for personal growth and happiness.</p>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-012.mp3" length="26648432"/>
              <guid>0a8059bd-7a55-406f-8eb0-1ae12039d3ef</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>17:8</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:53 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>The Life Coaching Minefield</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Nikita dislikes the coaching industry, but Vasily sees pros if the coaching raises energy and provides accountability. They discuss how to vet so-called gurus, and debate paid versus freely shared wisdom.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikita thinks most folks selling themselves as life coaches just want your cash. But Vasily says some coaches can help you get motivated to improve your life. Nikita warns about social media influencer types who act like gurus but don’t really know you. Vasily thinks hiring a coach can work if they get you taking action and hold you accountable.</p><p>They tell stories of coaches who were helpful and others who just talked big without delivering. In the end, Nikita and Vasily agree you need to be smart about who you take advice from. Not everyone who seems ultra confident has the answers. The trick is finding a mentor who calls you to be your best self, not just tells you what you want to hear.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Tim Ward’s YouTube Channel<strong> </strong><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/@TimothyWard">https://www.youtube.com/@TimothyWard</a></p></li><li><p>Pieter Levels on X (Twitter) <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://twitter.com/levelsio">https://twitter.com/levelsio</a></p></li><li><p>Darren Silver <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.darrensilver.earth/">https://www.darrensilver.earth/</a></p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-011.mp3" length="37022210"/>
              <guid>fc04a0e0-5ad1-4d8f-bf06-f36da59d64c0</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>23:55</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:03 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Anger Mismanagement</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily and Nikita get real about anger, sharing times they’ve lost their cool and debating if blowing off steam can actually lead to more chill. If you allow yourself to feel rage now and then, will it bring you Zen or just make you angrier?</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>During their discussion about anger and happiness, Vasily and Nikita get into a lively debate. They share personal stories about anger, revealing how it can affect people's behavior and emotions. The hosts discuss situations where anger emerged unexpectedly, like when a cab driver took a wrong route, and how people reacted. They examine the challenges of managing anger healthily, especially in today's society, where expressing anger can be challenging.</p><p>Vasily and Nikita also share their thoughts on the fine line between justified anger and destructive outbursts, emphasizing the importance of understanding and acknowledging this complex emotion. Throughout the episode, they touch on the discomfort and unease that often accompany anger and ponder the limited outlets available for expressing it.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.breakbarnyc.com/&nbsp;">Break Bar NYC</a></p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.ragecagenyc.com/">The Rage Cage in Brooklyn</a></p><p></p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-010.mp3" length="25005636"/>
              <guid>01827406-2bdb-4622-a362-4683ba213329</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>16:28</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 19:33 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Changing Through Therapy</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily and Nikita explain that therapy isn&apos;t about being crazy and that finding a therapist you trust is important. It&apos;s a good listen for anyone thinking about giving it a try.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode, Vasily and Nikita discuss therapy. They talk about why people might consider doing it as Vasily shares his personal journey trying therapy for the first time. They describe different therapeutic modalities, including Internal Family Systems (IFS). They talk about how IFS views individuals as having different inner "parts" or facets, each with its own role and voice, and how this approach can be liberating as it removes perceived judgment.</p><p>The episode emphasizes that therapy isn't about dealing with being "crazy" but self-improvement and seeking support when needed. Vasily explains why he decided to give therapy a try. They especially highlight the importance of finding a therapist you can trust.</p><p>It's a good listen for anyone curious about therapy or thinking about giving it a try.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0141842/">The Sopranos</a> – American crime drama TV series (IMDB)</p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt15677150/?ref_=fn_al_tt_1">Shrinking</a> – American sitcom series (IMDB)</p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://ifs-institute.com/&nbsp;">Internal Family Systems (IFS) official website</a>&nbsp;</p></li><li><p>The book <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.amazon.com/No-Bad-Parts-Restoring-Wholeness-ebook/dp/B096NHMV2R&nbsp;">"No Bad Parts" by Dr. Schwartz</a></p></li><li><p>Nikita's blog post <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://chepanov.com/above-all-else-we-want-to-be-understood/">'Above All Else, We Want to Be Understood'</a></p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-009.mp3" length="35480838"/>
              <guid>65e5294f-3226-4b80-9cbf-5435b863d99c</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>23:28</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 2 Oct 2023 10:59 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Tangled in Honesty</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily brought up a topic that caught Nikita off-guard: the concept of radical honesty and how it affects relationships</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode, Vasily threw Nikita a curveball with a topic that got him thinking. They dove into the unruly world of radical honesty and how it can mess with our relationships. Nikita brought up this idea of "right speech" from Buddhism, which caused Vasily to reflect.</p><p>Without intending to, the two friends turned the episode into an example of how radical honesty can be practiced since Nikita wasn’t a fan of how Vasily introduced the topic. Behind the scenes, they had to have a follow-up conversation ensuring their friendship was still strong after this little disagreement.&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_48_Laws_of_Power">Book 48 Laws of Power</a> (Wikipedia)&nbsp;</p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.learnreligions.com/right-speech-450072&nbsp;">Right Speech</a> (on 'Learn Religions') </p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Noble_Silence&nbsp;">Noble Silence in Buddhism</a> (Wikipedia) </p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://circlinginstitute.com/&nbsp;">The practice of Circling</a></p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tNA5qTTxFFA">Intro to Internal Family Systems</a> (YouTube)&nbsp;</p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-008.mp3" length="18790822"/>
              <guid>21382adb-0553-4ded-9e59-103b25c95c7a</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>14:59</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:18 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>When Sadness Sets In</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>The hosts explore the intricate relationship between sadness and personal growth, sharing practical methods to cope with unexplained sorrow and uncertainty.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode, the hosts have a conversation about the experience of feeling sad without any apparent reason. They discuss practical methods to cope with sadness, such as going for a walk, watching something enjoyable, talking to someone, or engaging in physical activity like going to the gym. They also mention actively meditating on negative emotions, allowing yourself to feel them without judgment.</p><p>Drawing from their own experiences, the hosts reflect on the power of self-awareness and recommend books like "Letting Go" and "Busting Loose from the Money Game" as resources for understanding and processing emotions. They emphasize the importance of embracing vulnerability and accepting the natural ebb and flow of emotions in life. They suggest finding solace in uncertainty. They point out that it's okay not always to be happy but to instead embrace and acknowledge their emotions as part of their personal growth journey.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Book “Letting Go” by David R. Hawkins <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://a.co/d/40lfrcR">https://a.co/d/40lfrcR</a>&nbsp;(Amazon)</p></li><li><p>Book “Busting Loose From The Money Game” by Robert Scheinfeld <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://a.co/d/cY6LzhO">https://a.co/d/cY6LzhO</a>&nbsp; and The Process (Tools: <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="http://www.robertscheinfeld.com/Scheinfeld-Drilling-Tools.pdf">http://www.robertscheinfeld.com/Scheinfeld-Drilling-Tools.pdf</a>)</p></li><li><p>Dr. Joe Dispenza <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.drjoedispenza.com">https://www.drjoedispenza.com</a>&nbsp;</p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-007.mp3" length="21760292"/>
              <guid>ef07e524-a1a0-49cf-9795-1b7309d4643d</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>14:31</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 4 Sep 2023 18:24 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Crafting Happiness Through Creativity</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>The hosts dive into the connection between creativity and happiness, discussing the impact of creative outlets on personal fulfillment</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode, the hosts explore how engaging in creative outlets can significantly impact our personal fulfillment. They reflect on their personal journeys of creativity, including writing blog posts, making music, and working on side projects, highlighting how these activities bring them joy and a sense of purpose.</p><p>They also touch upon the importance of public sharing and the unique satisfaction that comes from releasing creative work into the world.</p><p>While struggling to stay coherent during their conversation, Nikita and Vasily explore the connection between creativity and productivity, questioning whether a certain environment or being surrounded by others influences their motivation and ability to create.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://vasilym.com/blog">Vasily’s blog</a></p></li><li><p>Nikita’s <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://chepanov.com/irreconcilable-differences/">blog post on toxic positivity</a></p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qvk0YpGMGZM">Sonic Focus tune on YouTube (60m)</a></p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://open.spotify.com/track/3pdSxLx2CYmPvnGiTZZaoe">Sonic Focus tune on Spotify (12m)</a></p></li><li><p>Happy Maybe <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://happymaybe.com/2023/08/the-never-ending-quest-for-home/&nbsp;">Episode 5 'The Never-ending Quest For Home"</a></p><p></p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-006.mp3" length="18070691"/>
              <guid>b1f0f2d5-2c81-4e29-bd36-651d8495c77d</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>14:27</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:41 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>The Never-Ending Quest for Home</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily, Nikita, and guest Liya delve into the complexities of choosing a place to call home, exploring the desire for novelty, building connections, and finding balance in their pursuit of happiness in this captivating episode of Happy Maybe.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>Join Vasily, Nikita, and special guest Liya in this fascinating episode of Happy Maybe, where they discuss the difficulties of choosing where to live and the excitement of exploring new things. They talk about the importance of having a community, the thrill of traveling, and finding the right balance between stability and adventure.</p><p>We hope this conversation will help you consider new perspectives on where you belong and discover happiness in unexpected places.</p><p>Here is the breakdown of the episode.</p><ol>  <li>    Exploring new places and seeking <strong>novelty</strong>.  </li>  <li>    Balancing <strong>community</strong> and the desire for adventure.  </li>  <li>    Challenges of building <strong>connections</strong> in new environments.  </li>  <li>    Finding <strong>stability</strong> amidst the thrill of discovery.  </li>  <li>    The influence of the "<strong>honeymoon</strong> period" on perceptions.  </li>  <li>    The ongoing quest for happiness and fulfillment in <strong>choosing a place to live</strong>.  </li></ol>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-005.mp3" length="20464466"/>
              <guid>e9b03170-2095-40ee-b7c4-46cdd704adeb</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>16:12</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 7 Aug 2023 19:40 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>When Success Isn&apos;t Enough</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily and Nikita questioned whether constantly trying to improve yourself and pushing for professional success lead to happiness and fulfillment. They also discuss the dilemma of whether to ask for a salary raise or just accept the status quo.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Happy Maybe, Vasily and Nikita engage in a freeform conversation about the complexities of finding happiness and satisfaction in a seemingly "perfect" life. They explore the pressures of constantly striving for self-improvement and question whether pursuing professional success always leads to happiness. They also delve into the dilemma of whether to push for a salary raise or accept the status quo. Join them for a thought-provoking conversation that challenges our assumptions about what truly matters in life.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p>On <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2020/09/joseph-henrich-explores-weird-societies/&nbsp;">WEIRD societies</a></p></li><li><p>Nikita’s <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://chepanov.com/irreconcilable-differences/">blog post on toxic positivity</a></p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-004.mp3" length="24750763"/>
              <guid>fc2e96fd-3fb9-4eb7-9427-4b9f866ef487</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>14:0</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:22 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Inspiration vs. Discipline</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>The hosts engage in a freeform conversation about the connection between inspiration, discipline, and our pursuit of happiness.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Happy Maybe, Vasily and Nikita engage in a freeform conversation about the connection between inspiration, discipline, and our pursuit of happiness. Nikita shares how his recent trip to Costa Rica inspired him, but his motivation has since waned. Vasily discusses his personal struggle with maintaining a consistent meditation practice and suggests reading books as a more mindful alternative to mindlessly scrolling through social media.</p><p>Tune in to this episode and join the freeform conversation between two friends as they share their insights on what drives us towards happiness.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Old Chinese tale <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_old_man_lost_his_horse ">“The Story of the Old Man and His Horse"</a> (that the hosts called “The Maybe Tale”)</p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/therapy-types/internal-family-systems-therapy">Internal Family Systems Therapy</a> (article)</p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-003.mp3" length="37036946"/>
              <guid>237a2f3b-2812-4bfc-b223-71345077147d</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>21:52</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:25 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Cultural Crossroads and Quest For Belonging</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Exploring the challenges and triumphs of adapting to life in a new culture; the journey of immigration, and the pursuit of a sense of belonging.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Happy Maybe, Vasily and Nikita explore the challenges of having an identity as an immigrant. They delve into the complex process of cultural integration and discuss how it can be a never-ending struggle that lasts for years. Drawing from their own experiences, Vasily and Nikita share insights on how to navigate the ups and downs of adapting to a new culture and finding a sense of belonging.</p><p>Tune in to this freeform conversation between two friends for a heartfelt and thought-provoking discussion on what it means to have an identity shaped by immigration.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gogol_Bordello">Gogol Bordello (band)</a> &nbsp;</p></li><li><p><a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/gogolbordello">Gogol Bordello YouTube channel</a>&nbsp;</p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-002.mp3" length="19009275"/>
              <guid>fb3421e9-426a-405c-a66e-e54467b46700</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>15:19</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:00 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
        <item>
              <title>Less-Than-Ideal Choices</title>
              <itunes:subtitle>Vasily and Nikita explore the complexities of making tough choices in a world of competing perspectives in the debut episode.</itunes:subtitle>
              
              <description><![CDATA[<p>In the debut episode of Happy Maybe (which was still an unnamed podcast at the time of the recording), Vasily and Nikita dive into a nuanced conversation about the difficulties of taking sides when faced with two less-than-ideal options. From navigating personal relationships to grappling with divisive political issues, they explore the complexities of making tough choices.</p><p>Join them for a gripping conversation on how to find a way forward in a world of competing perspectives.</p><p><strong>Links:</strong></p><ul><li><p>Nikita’s blog <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://chepanov.com/">https://chepanov.com/</a>&nbsp;</p></li><li><p>Peace Pilgrim (book) <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" href="https://www.peacepilgrim.org/translations">https://www.peacepilgrim.org/translations</a>&nbsp;</p></li></ul>]]></description>
              <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="https://happymaybe.s3.amazonaws.com/audio/hm-001.mp3" length="37604138"/>
              <guid>c6654670-7123-4d23-9519-6f6091c33dd6</guid>
              
              <itunes:duration>25:28</itunes:duration>
              <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
              
              <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:00 UTC</pubDate>
          </item>
            
      </channel>
      <!-- Generated by Indeecast -->
  </rss>
      